

https://www.mayurdiar.com maydiar@gmail.com 🕼

www.linkedin.com/in/mayurdiar in

678.860.0120

# **ABOUT ME**

Forward-thinking UX/UI & Graphic Designer with a certificate in UX/UI from Georgia Institute of Technology, an MBA from Keller Graduate School of Management and a BFA in Graphic Design from The Art Institute of Atlanta, with experience in Adobe CC, Invision, definition & ideation, prototyping and testing, interaction design, branding and HTML/CSS.

# **EDUCATION**

#### GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

UX/UI Certificate Program Atlanta, GA | 2020

#### KELLER GRADUATE SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT

Master of Business Administration -**Business Administration and Management** Atlanta, GA | 2012

#### THE ART INSTITUTE OF ATLANTA

Bachelor of Fine Arts - Graphic Design Atlanta, GA | 2004

# SKILLS + TOOLS

### **DESIGN SKILLS**

User Experience Design User Interface Design Product Design Visual Design Interaction Design Graphic Design Branding + Identity **Typography** 

## **PERSONAL SKILLS**

**Great Communicator Problem Solver** Critical Thinker **Detail-Oriented** Leadership Great Time Management Organized Collaborative

# **UX METHODS**

Research + Analysis **User Personas** Ideation Wireframing Prototyping **Usability Testing Evaluation + Iteration** 

#### **TOOLS**







# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **EQUIFAX**

Lead UX/UI Designer Atlanta, GA | October 2021 - Present

- · Create global consistency in solving user needs and interactions while adhering to brand guidelines.
- · Create wireframes and storyboards of information flow and user journeys that support stakeholder goals.
- Communicate design ideas and prototypes to developers by creating clear functional requirements and design specifications.
- Continuously improve on the global platform through user testing and research.
- Contribute to and uphold the company's Design System to standardize external web facing properties.

#### **CIOX HEALTH**

**UX Design Engineer** 

Alpharetta, GA | March 2021 - October 2021

- Collaborated with team members to analyze and make recommendations to improve current internal and external software and applications and build concepts for future applications.
- · Created low-fidelity sketches and wireframes that represent the proposed value for stakeholders. executives, and end-users.
- Built prototypes to streamline the design development process, test the interface elements, and represent the overall vision.
- · Conducted user testing to identify potential issues and collect feedback for necessary changes.
- · Negotiated engineering changes and roadblocks throughout the construction process and offer solutions to challenges discovered on the way.

## **COX AUTOMOTIVE**

**Advertising Operations Lead** Digital Media Designer (UX/UI) Atlanta, GA | December 2011 - March 2020

- · Created a variety of products, including dataset driven flash ads to complex, user centered UX/UI rich media products for desktop, mobile and tablet.
- Participated in the entire UX process, from concept through completion. Created sketches, wireframes, user flows, low & high-fidelity prototypes and sitemaps.
- Worked with cross-functional groups to maximize new product testing, implementation and troubleshooting.
- Strengthened cross-departmental relationships to identify key growth opportunities within operations.
- · Oversaw training and coaching for all new employees that has exceeded new hire performance goals by over 20% since 2015.